saanapay.com 2018-08-20

# SaanaPay™ - Fast, Secure, Reliable Payments

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. You accepted this policy when you signed up for our service. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it.

#### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

When you visit the SaanaPay website, we collect your IP address and standard web log information. Such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website.

#### If you open an account, we collect the following types of information from you:

  * Contact information-your name, address, phone, email, and other similar information.
  * Financial information - the bank account numbers and credit card numbers that you link to your SaanaPay account.

Before permitting you to use our service, we may reqire you to provide additional information we can use to verify your identity or address or manage risk, such as your date of birth, or other information. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as credit bureaus and identify verification services.

When you are using our service, we collect information about your account transactions and we may collect information about your computer or other access device for fraud prevention purposes.

Finally, we may collect additional information about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey.

#### **THE USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**

When you access our websites or use related SaanaPay services, we may place small data files on your computer or other device. These data files may be cookies, pixel tags, "Flash cookies," or other local storage provided by your browser or associated applications (collectively referred to as "Cookies"). These technologies are used to recognize users as customers; customize SaanaPay Services, content, and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness; help ensure that account security is not compromised; mitigate risk and prevent fraud; and to promote trust and safety across SaanaPay Services and related sites.

Users can freely decline our Cookies if the web browser or browser add-on permits, unless our Cookies are required to prevent fraud or ensure the security of websites we control. However, declining our Cookies may interfere with your use of our websites and SaanaPay Services.

#### **HOW WE PROTECT AND STORE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymised so that it does not identify a specific user.

We store and process your personal information on our computer and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws of Nigeria. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorise access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfil their job responsibilities.

#### **HOW WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customised experience. We may use your personal information to:**

  * Provide the services and customer support you request;
  * Process transactions and send notices about your transactions;
  * Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;
  * Customise, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website;
  * Send you targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers bases on your communication preferences;
  * Compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.

#### **HOW WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHER SAANAPAY USERS**

To process your payments, we need to share some of your personal information with the person or company that you are paying or is paying you. Your contact information, date of sign-up, the number of payments you have received from verified SaanaPay users, and whether you have verified control of a bank account are provided to other SaanaPay users who you transact with through SaanaPay. 

If you are buying goods or services and pay through SaanaPay, the seller is not allowed to use this information to market their services to you unless you have agreed to it.

We work with merchants to enable them to accept payments from you using SaanaPay. In doing so, a merchant may share information about you with us, with your email address, when you attempt to pay that merchant. We use this information to confirm to that merchant that you are a SaanaPay customer and that the merchant should enable SaanaPay as a form of payment for your purchase.

Regardless, we will not disclose your credit card number, ATM Card number or bank account number to anyone you have paid or who has paid you through SaanaPay, except with your express permission or if we are required to do so to comply with a subpoena or other legal process.

#### **HOW WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHER PARTIES**

**We may share your personal information with:**

  * Service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations; (fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, technology services). Our contracts dictate that these service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit.
  * Financial institution that we partner with, where we share information. These financial institutions may only use this information to market SaanaPay-related products, unless you have given consent for other uses.
  * Credit bureaus to report outstanding negative balance accounts, as allowed by law.
  * Companies that we plan to merge with or be acquired by. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information could be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.
  * Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure
  * We need to do so to comply with law
  * We believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our User Agreement.
  * Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.
  * SaanaPay will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.

#### **HOW YOU CAN RESTRICT SAANAPAY FROM SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Federal and State laws allow you to restrict the sharing of your personal information in certain instances. However, these laws also state that you cannot restrict other types of sharing . Because we have chosen to refrain from certain types of data sharing, the only type of sharing of your personal information that you may restrict is as follows:

If you do not want SaanaPay to share your personal information with any third party for marketing purposes, you may send an email to that effect to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/web/20180820211939id_/http%3A//saanapay.com/support@saanapay.ng) You can also control how we use your contact information to market our services to you in the notifications preferences.

#### **HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CHANGE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging into your account and navigating to the settings option. 

You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging into your account and navigating to the settings option.
